Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/rafay-ahmed-1b83681a1 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Software Quality Assurance Selenium Manual Testing

Rafay Ahmed

FinTech | Implementation | Testing | Application Consultant at Euronet Worldwide

Karāchi

Summary

As a skilled IT professional with experience in Software Development. I want to join a progressive firm which will make use of my talent and experience. I have this self learning attitude which helps me tackle resistance and overcoming pressures also I am passionate and interested in working as SQA Engineer.

Experience

Euronet Worldwide Associate Application Consultant August 2021 - Present (8 months) Karachi, Sindh, Pakistan

Synergy Inc.
Technical Consultant
January 2021 - March 2021 (3 months)
Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Education

PAF-Karachi Institute of Economics & Technology Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2016 - 2021)